Ricketts mss. III, 1856-1979 LMC 1831
Lilly Library
Ricketts mss. III
1856-1979
Lilly Library
LMC 1831
80 linear feet 56 boxes
The Ricketts mss. III, 1856-1979, consist of the papers and correspondence of Coella Lindsay Ricketts, 1859-1941, calligrapher and illuminator, and of the work of The Scriptorium operated by Ricketts in Chicago.
Lilly - Stacks (Box 44); Wells - Map Case; Vault 2 (Box 29, 30); ALF (Auxiliary Library Facility)
Access Restrictions
Access to this collection requires advance notice. Please contact the curator for additional information.
Biographical Note
Coella Lindsay Ricketts, 1859-1941, was a renowned calligrapher and illuminator of Chicago, Illinois. Ricketts founded The Scriptorium, a firm specializing in calligraphy and illuminations, in 1885.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into the following series: Personal, Correspondence, Financial, Scriptorium, Subject Files, Writings and Book/Manuscript Collections, Medieval Fragments and Illuminations, and Miscellaneous.
Scope and Content Note
Included are files for the period when The Scriptorium was managed by his daughter, Julia (Ricketts) King, and his son-in-law, Jasper Seymour King. With the collection are medieval and historical documents assembled by C.L. Ricketts, ranging from the 13th century to 1848.
The first series of the collection, Personal, consists of biographical materials, 1856-1963, for Helen Louise (Ricketts) Goodman, Julia Marguerite (Ricketts) King, Coella Lindsay Ricketts, Hettie (Merriam) Ricketts, and several other members of the Ricketts family. Also included are materials relating to penmanship classes and exercises designed and taught by Ricketts as well as memorabilia from his membership to the Caxton Club and his involvement with the World's Columbian Exposition.
The second series, Correspondence, contains the correspondence and business papers, 1875-1979, including letters to Ricketts from his wife Hettie written while he was in Europe and she was running the business in Chicago; letters from employees during his absences; correspondence with European acquaintances, scholars, and dealers in books on calligraphy; and letters of introduction for Ricketts from American diplomats and others to European institutions and individuals owning manuscripts. Some of the letters from Europe during World War I comment on the war. Other correspondence includes letters to Ricketts in Chicago from Hettie and their two daughters, Helen and Julia, while the three of them were in Europe, 1909-1910.
The Financial series includes bank records; bookseller invoices; business records for The Scriptorium; invoices; medical receipts; North Shore Syndicate papers; property deeds and real estate taxes; materials relating to Ricketts' second-hand book business that he operated in the early 1900's; and stocks and bonds.
The Scriptorium series consists of materials relating to and created by the Scriptorium, including designs, specimens, realia, and texts collected for ideas. Included in this series are the materials for The Book, a collection prepared by Ricketts to illustrate the development of the alphabet from the 7th to the 15th centuries as found in medieval documents.
Subject Files consist of informational clippings and pamphlets/specimens arranged by subject.
Writings and Book/Manuscript Collections includes writings by Ricketts as well as writings by others. Also included are writings about Ricketts' collections of books and manuscripts, as well as notes, bibliographies, and other related materials.
The bulk of Medieval Fragments and Illuminations consists of photographs, modern holograph reproductions, and facsimiles of illuminated manuscripts and bindings arranged by collector/institution or type of material, as well as some 19th century illuminations and bindings. Also included are 100 fragments, most of which are medieval but some of which date from the 18th and 19th centuries.
Note on Indexing Term - "Women": Includes a number of letters written by Alameda Virginia (Ricketts) Smith, Julia Marguerite (Ricketts) King and Mehitable Henrietta Hester Ann (Merriam) Ricketts.
Note on Indexing Term - "World War, 1914-1918": There are some letters from Europe during World War I which comment on the war.
Related Material
See Ricketts mss. and Ricketts mss. II, also located at the Lilly Library, Indiana University, Bloomington, Indiana.
Acquisition Information
Gift: 1982, 1983
Women; World War, 1914-1918; Illumination of books and manuscripts; Ricketts, C. L. (Coella Lindsay), 1859-1941
- Personal
  - Goodman, Helen Louise (Ricketts) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    [fill in from binder]
  - King, Julia Marguerite (Ricketts) and Jasper Seymour King (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Memorabilia, 2 Folders (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - Ricketts, Coella Lindsay, 12 Folders (Box 1, Folder 5-16)
  - Advertisements for CLR's work, membership certificates, and photo of CLR (Map case 2)
  - Ricketts, Hettie (Merriam) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Ricketts family (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ricketts family photographs (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Caxton Club
    Includes announcements of meetings, bills, minutes, publications, papers, but no correspondence
    - 1900-1910 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      Includes original illumination for Annual Meeting on Feb. 3, 1900
    - 1911-1915 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      Includes subscription cards from William C. Bobbs of Indianapolis and C. L. Ricketts for copies of Souvestre, the Attic Philosopher in Paris; List of Exhibitions and Addresses for 1917-1920
    - 1918 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      Includes an account by C. L. Ricketts of the Caxton Club Exhibit at the Art Institute, as printed in the Bulletin of the Art Institute of Chicago, March 1918; Caxton Club publications, prices and sales
    - 1919 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - 1920 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - 1921-1926 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 18, Folder 29)
      Includes minutes for February 5, 1927, which records the death of William C. Bobbs, Feb. 11, 1926
    - 1929 (Box 18, Folder 30)
      Includes brochure to Members about the publication of the monograph on "Roger Payne, English Bookbinder of the Eighteenth Century"
    - 1930-1935 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Caxton Club emblem (Box 18, Folder 33)
      Eight drawings
  - Exhibits and Loans
    - 1918 (Box 19, Folder 59)
      See also Caxton Club
    - 1919 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - 1930 (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 61-62)
    - 1931 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - 1932 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - 1933 (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 65-66)
    - 1934 (Box 19, Folder 67)
      "Visitors to the Treasure Room, Northwestern Library, Evanston, Illinois," July 24-October 31, 1934. Names include those of Lulu Ricketts, Red Lodge, Montana, and Mrs. C. E. Ricketts, Park Ridge, Illinois, about the first of October, 1934 [lb] See also letter of August 14, 1934, from Dorothy (daughter of George Mason Ricketts) mentioning "Uncle's exhibit at the Library"
    - 1940 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - 1943 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - 1947 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - 1949 (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - 1961 (Box 19, Folder 72)
      At the Lilly Library, Indiana University, Bloomington. Includes speeches made by Jasper S. King and Julia (Ricketts) King on this occasion. Three drafts of Mrs. King's speech written on verso of the Van Orman Suburban Hotel stationery
    - Undated - Exhibits (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - Undated - Loans (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Illuminated exhibit sign for Ricketts collection (Box 36)
  - Names and addresses (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Names and addresses of contact persons for CLR, holograph and printed, American and European
  - Penmanship classes
    - Schedules and financial records, 1887-1892 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Students' copywork, 1881-1887 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Students' copywork, 1888 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Students' copywork, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Exercise work (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Winnetka Congregational Church, 1931-1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Church programs with occasional personal notes by Julia Ricketts King
  - World's Columbian Exposition, 1893 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Photos - friends of CLR (Box 39)
  - Photos - family of CLR (Box 39)
  - Photos - CLR (Box 39)
  - Award - World's Columbian Exposition to C. L. Ricketts for his illuminated works (Box 53)
- Correspondence
  - 1875-1877 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1878 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 1879 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 1880 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 1881 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 1882, January-June (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 1882, July-December (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 1883, January-June (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 1883, July-December (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 1884, January-July (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 1884, August-December (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 1885, January-March (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 1885, April-June (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 1885, July-September (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 1885, October (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 1885, November (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - 1885, December (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 1886, January (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1886, February 1-15 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1886, February 16-28 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1886, March (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1886, April (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1886, May (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1886, June (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1886, July-September (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1886, October (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1886, November (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1886, December (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1887, January (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1887, February-December (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1888-1889 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 1890-1891 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 1892 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 1893 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 1894 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 1895 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 1896 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 1897 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 1898, January-July (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 1898, August (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 1898, September (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 1898, October-December (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 1899, January-June (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 1899, July-December (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 1900, January-March (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 1900, April-May (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 1900, June-December (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 1901, January-May (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - 1901, June-July (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - 1901, August (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 1901, September-December (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - 1902, January-May (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - 1902, June-July (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - 1902, August-December (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - 1903, January-May (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - 1903, June-December (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1904, January-March (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1904, April (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1904, May-July (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1904, August-December (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1905, January-March (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1905, April-May (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1905, June-December (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 1906, January-March (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1906, April-June (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1906, July-August (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1906, September-December (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 1907, January-March (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 1907, April-July (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 1907, August (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 1907, September (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 1907, October 1-19 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - 1907, October 20-31 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 1907, November (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 1907, December 1-19 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 1907, December 20-31 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 1908, January-March (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - 1908, April-May (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 1908, June-July (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - 1908, August-September (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - 1908, October-November (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - 1908, December (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 1909, January-March (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 1909, April-May (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 1909, June-July (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - 1909, August (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - 1909, September-October (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1909, November (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1909, December (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1910, January (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1910, February (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1910, March (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1910, April (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 1910, May (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 1910, June (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 1910, July 1-21 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 1910, July 22-31 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 1910, August (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 1910, September (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1910, October 1-17 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 1910, October 18-31 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 1910, November (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 1910, December 1-14 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 1910, December 15-31 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 1911, January 1-20 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 1911, January 21-31 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 1911, February (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - 1911, March-April (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - 1911, May (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - 1911, June (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - 1911, July (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - 1911, August-October (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 1911, November (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1911, December (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1912, January (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1912, February-June (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1912, July-September (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1912, October (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1912, November (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1912, December 1-15 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 1912, December 16-24 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 1912, December 25-31 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 1913, January 1-20 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 1913, January 21-31 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 1913, February 1-14 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 1913, February 15-28 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 1913, March 1-10 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 1913, March 11-20 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 1913, March 21-31 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 1913, April (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 1913, May-June (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - 1913, July-August (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - 1913, September-November (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - 1913, December (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 1914, January (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - 1914, February (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - 1914, March (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - 1914, April-May (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - 1914, June (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - 1914, July (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - 1914, August-October (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1914, November-December (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1915, January (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1915, February (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1915, March (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1915, April-May (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1915, June (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1915, July-August (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 1915, September-October (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 1915, November (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 1915, December (Box 6, Folder 10.5)
  - 1916, January (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1916, February (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1916, March 1-12 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1916, March 13-31 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1916, April (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1916, May (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 1916, June-July (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 1916, August (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 1916, September (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 1916, October-November (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 1916, December (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - 1917, January (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 1917, February (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - 1917, March (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - 1917, April (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - 1917, May-June (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - 1917, July-September (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - 1917, October-December (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - 1918, January-February (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - 1918, March-April (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - 1918, May-June (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - 1918, July-September (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - 1918, October (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - 1918, November (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - 1918, December (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - 1919, January (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1919, February (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 1919, March (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1919, April (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 1919, May (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 1919, June (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1919, July-August (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 1919, September (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1919, October-December (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 1920, January (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 1920, February (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 1920, March (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 1920, April (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 1920, May (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 1920, June (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 1920, July (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 1920, August (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - 1920, September-October (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - 1920, November-December (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - 1921, January-February (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 1921, March (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - 1921, April-May (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 1921, June-July (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 1921, August-Octboer (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 1921, November-December (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - 1922, January (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - 1922, February-March (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - 1922, April 1-17 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - 1922, April 19-31 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - 1922, May-July (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - 1922, August-October (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - 1922, November 1-15 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - 1922, November 16-31 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 1922, December 1-10 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 1922, December 11-18 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 1922, December 19-25 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - 1922, December 26-31 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - 1923, January 1-15 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - 1923, January 16-31 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - 1923, February 1-15 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - 1923, February 16-28 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - 1923, March (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1923, April (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1923, May (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1923, June-July (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1923, August-October (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 1923, November-December (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1924, January (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1924, February (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1924, March-May (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1924, June-July 17 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1924, July 18-31 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 1924, August (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 1924, September-October (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 1924, November (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 1924, December 1-16 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 1924, December 17-31 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 1925, January 1-15 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - 1925, January 16-31 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 1925, February 1-8 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 1925, February 9-16 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 1925, February 17-28 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 1925, March (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 1925, April (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 1925, May (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - 1925, June (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - 1925, July (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - 1925, August (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - 1925, September-October (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - 1925, November (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - 1925, December (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - 1925-1926 correspondence fragments (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - 1926, January (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - 1926, February (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - 1926, March 1-11 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - 1926, March 12-31 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - 1926, April (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - 1926, May (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - 1926, June (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - 1926, July (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - 1926, August (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - 1926, September 1-13 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - 1926, September 14-30 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - 1926, October (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - 1926, November 1-12 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 1926, November 13-30 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 1926, December 1-10 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 1926, December 11-31 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 1927, January 1-10 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 1927, January 11-31 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1927, February (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 1927, March 1-14 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 1927, March 15-31 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 1927, March 3 - Whiley, George M. to C.L.R. with 33 enclosures of vellum (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 1927, April 1-13 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 1927, April 14-31 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 1927, May (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 1927, June (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 1927, July-September (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 1927, October-November (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 1927, December (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 1928, January (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 1928, February-March (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - 1928, April (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - 1928, May (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - 1928, June-July (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - 1928, August-September (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - 1928, October (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - 1928, November (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - 1928, December 1-17 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - 1928, December 18-21 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - 1928, December 22-31 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - 1929, January 1-9 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - 1929, January 10-31 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - 1929, February (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - 1929, March (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - 1929, April (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - 1929, May (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - 1929, June (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - 1929, July (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - 1929, August (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - 1929, September (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - 1929, October (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - 1929, November-December 10 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 1929, December 11-19 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 1929, December 20-24 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 1929, December 25-31 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 1930, January 1-20 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 1930, January 21-31 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 1930, February (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 1930, March 1-11 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 1930, March 12-31 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 1930, April (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 1930, May (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 1930, June (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 1930, July (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 1930, August 1-19 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 1930, August 20-31 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - 1930, September (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 1930, October (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 1930, November (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 1930, December 1-15 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 1930, December 16-31 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - 1931, January (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - 1931, February (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - 1931, March (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - 1931, April 1-16 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - 1931, April 17-30 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - 1931, May (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - 1931, June (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - 1931, July (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - 1931, August (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - 1931, September (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - 1931, October-November (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - 1931, December (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - 1932, January (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - 1932, February (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - 1932, March (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - 1932, April (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - 1932, May (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - 1932, June (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - 1932, July (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - 1932, August (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - 1932, September-October (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - 1932, November-December (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - 1933, January (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - 1933, February (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - 1933, March (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - 1933, April (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - 1933, May-June (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1933, July-October (Box 11, Folder 1.5)
  - 1933, November-December (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1934, January-February (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1934, March-April (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1934, May (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1934, June-August (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1934, September-December (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1935, January (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 1935, February-March (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 1935, April-May (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 1935, June (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 1935, July (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 1935, August (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 1935, September (Box 11, Folder 13.5)
  - 1935, October-November (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 1935, December (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 1936, January-April (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - 1936, May-October (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 1936, November-December (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 1937, January-June (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - 1937, July-September (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - 1937, October-December (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - 1938, January-July (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - 1938, August-December (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - 1939, January-February (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - 1939, March 1-10 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - 1939, March 11-31 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - 1939, April (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - 1939, May-August (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - 1939, September-December (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - 1942 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - 1943 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - 1944-1947 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - 1948 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - 1949 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - 1950 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - 1953 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - 1954 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - 1957 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - 1958 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - 1959 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - 1960 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1961 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 1962 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 1963 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 1964 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 1964, January 20 - Baur George to King, Jasper S. With enclosures (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 1965 (Box 12, Folder 7)